styleblueprint.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

## StyleBlueprint Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

StyleBlueprint may provide to a third party an anonymous version of user information. Such third party may use that information to link to and issue an anonymous cookie containing demographic or intent-based data. Such cookies do not contain personally identifiable information.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

This site is being monitored by additional third-party monitoring software, and may capture information about your visit that will help us improve the quality of our service.  You many opt-out of any such monitoring by enabling “Do Not Track” settings on your browser.  Please [click here for instructions](https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2012/06/how-turn-do-not-track-your-browser) for setup on your computer.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

– To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

– To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

– To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

– To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

– To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Third-Party Service Providers

In order to serve you better, we may at times contract with other companies (“Service Providers”) to help us process information. For instance, their assistance can help us better fulfill customer orders, manage, store and enhance customer data, and comply with eCommerce regulations. For your security, these companies are bound by our nondisclosure agreements or other contractual arrangements to provide privacy protection for your information.

We use a Service Provider to send emails that you have agreed to receive. Web cookies are used in those email messages and at our Websites to help us measure the effectiveness of those emails and for other analytical purposes. You can “opt out” of this email cookie at any time by clicking the link at the footer of any StyleBlueprint marketing email or by emailing support@styleblueprint.com

We contract with Service Providers to place our banner advertising on other websites. These Service Providers may collect information from us about your visits to our Websites and stores, and your interaction with our products and services. They also may use this information to tailor banner advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry-standard technology used by most major websites. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, personally identifiable information may be shared with our Service Provider and its service providers, including, without limitation, your name, postal address and email address, as well as a record of any transactions you conduct on our Website or offline in order to deliver banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites. Our trusted Service Provider will keep this data anonymous and will not share any personally identifiable information with any other third parties. Please visit the Network Advertising Initiative (<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>) to learn more about the use of this information by our Service Provider or to choose limited use of this information by opting out of interest-based online advertising.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 11/10/2013

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://support.styleblueprint.com  
PO 150948  
Nashville, TN 37215  
email@styleblueprint.com  
615-988-4556
